CURRICULUM VITAE

MICHAIL

(+62) 813-1409-2890

Jl. Kp Duri Barat no 23b

https://michailtjhang.github.io/

github.com/michailtjhang

👩 🕥 @michailtj39



ABOUT ME

I am a 20-year-old teenager. I am interested in the world of programming. I always want to learn new things and improve my skills in IT. I can also organize a team and solve problems well. I hope to be accepted as an intern with your company and make a positive contribution.

EXPERIENCE

· January 2022 - Present

Head Leader Multimedia Youth Abbalove

Responsible for managing the multimedia team. Organize the schedule of multimedia members needed for each activity or event held by Youth Abbalove. Provide training and guidance to multimedia team members who have just joined or who want to improve their skills. Evaluate and provide feedback to multimedia team members to improve their performance and creativity.

August 2023 - December 2023

Independent Study Batch 5, Fullstack Web Developer, PT Hendevane Indonesia

- Develop web-based applications using the Laravel Framework.
- · Learned basic web development materials, and deployed projects to github and hosting,
- Learning other programming languages including forming a project development framework, namely React JS.

PROJECT

TrackMyShipment, Backend Developer | Desember 2023

https://peserta31.msib5.hendevane.com/TrackMyShipment/

- Technology used: HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), Javascript, and PHP as Laravel Framework.
- Develop a web application that allows users to send packages/goods to the destination in realtime.
- Allows users to track packages, check shipping costs, and TrackMyShipment e-wallet features.

EDUCATION

2021 - Present Dian Nusantara University Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering

2018 - 2021 Santo Paulus High School Jakarta Science Department

SOFT SKILL & SOFTWARE

- · Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint Good
- · Propresenter, EasyWorship Good
- · Canva, Corel Draw Good
- Team Organizer Good
- Problem Solver Good

HARDSKILL PEMOGRAMAN

- C++, Java Basic
- HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript Good
- Sql (MySQL, SQLite) Good
- Framework (Laravel) Good
- · Libary (React JS) Basic
- Node JS Good
- · GIT & Github Good
- UI & UX (Figma) Good